So what is quizket he's kid
では、Qiskitとは何でしょうか？
kissed kiskin is an open source software development kit
Qiskitは、オープンソースのソフトウェア開発キットです。
for working with quantum computers
量子コンピューターを使って作業するための
at the level of circuits
circuit のレベルで、
algorithms and application modules this sdk
アルゴリズムやアプリケーションモジュールも扱えます。このSDKは
allows anyone to program on real quantity computers from
誰でも自分のノートパソコンから実際の量子コンピューターにアクセスして
their laptop in two lines of code you can access
プログラムできます。わずか2行のコードで
several quantum systems ranging from super conducting
超伝導から
to trapped iron cubits want to emulate a quantum computer's
トラップイオン qubit まで、複数の量子システムにアクセスできます。量子コンピューターの
behavior instead change a single line of code
動作をエミュレートしたい場合は、1行変えるだけで
and simulate your quantum circuits on our high performance
高性能な quantum circuit のシミュレーションも可能です。
simulate kiss get is a tool used by tens of
Qiskitは世界中の何万人もの人々に使われているツールで、
thousands of people global war all try to
皆さんが未来を作ろうと取り組んでいます。
build the future whether your researcher developer
研究者でも、開発者でも、
or just looking to get started
これから始めたい方でも、
kissed it has a number of
Qiskitにはさまざまな
features available for your needs
ニーズに応える機能が用意されています。
allowing anyone to do things
誰でも、たとえば
like building your first quantum circuit
初めての quantum circuit を作ったり、
run cross domain quantum out of them
分野を超えた量子アルゴリズムを実行したり、
and study fundamental quantum phenomenon
量子現象の基礎を学んだりすることができます。
maybe now is the perfect time to get involved yourself
今こそ、あなた自身が関わるのに最適な時期かもしれません。
and find all the tools you need
必要なツールがすべて揃っています。
including real quantity machines
実際の量子コンピューターも含めて、
and sd k through kisking
Qiskitを通じてSDKにアクセスできます。
and a community that is happy to welcome
そして、あなたを温かく迎え、
and answers any questions you may have along the way
道中のどんな質問にも答えてくれるコミュニティがあります。
you can get started today
今日からでも始められます。
at kiss
Qiskitで。